[
  {
    "name": "Prvi seeder kviz",
    "description": "Ovo je prvi kviz",
    "q_and_a": [
      {
        "question": "What's the price of a mile?",
        "answers": ["50000", "60000", "70000", "80000"],
        "correct": "50000"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who won the war of 1812?",
        "answers": ["Brits", "Americans", "Russians", "Bulgarians"],
        "correct": "Russians"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is Desert Fox?",
        "answers": ["Bagration", "Rommel", "Blucher", "Igorov"],
        "correct": "Rommel"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is best commander in history?",
        "answers": ["Napoleon", "Marmont", "Alexander", "Caesar"],
        "correct": "Napoleon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which nationality was Svetozar Borojević",
        "answers": ["Austrian", "Slovak", "Croat", "Russian"],
        "correct": "Croat"
      }
    ],
    "user": "5f67b1607df2e42008681177"
  },
  {
    "name": "Drugi seeder kviz",
    "description": "Ovo je drugi kviz",
    "q_and_a": [
      {
        "question": "What's the price of a mile?_2",
        "answers": ["50000_2", "60000_2", "70000_2", "80000_2"],
        "correct": "50000_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who won the war of 1812?_2",
        "answers": ["Brits_2", "Americans_2", "Russians_2", "Bulgarians_2"],
        "correct": "Russians_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is Desert Fox?_2",
        "answers": ["Bagration_2", "Rommel_2", "Blucher_2", "Igorov_2"],
        "correct": "Rommel_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is best commander in history?",
        "answers": ["Napoleon", "Marmont", "Alexander", "Caesar"],
        "correct": "Marmont"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which nationality was Svetozar Borojević",
        "answers": ["Austrian", "Slovak", "Croat", "Russian"],
        "correct": "Croat"
      }
    ],
    "user": "5f67b1607df2e42008681177"
  },
  {
    "name": "Drugi seeder kviz1",
    "description": "Ovo je drugi kviz",
    "q_and_a": [
      {
        "question": "What's the price of a mile?_2",
        "answers": ["50000_2", "60000_2", "70000_2", "80000_2"],
        "correct": "50000_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who won the war of 1812?_2",
        "answers": ["Brits_2", "Americans_2", "Russians_2", "Bulgarians_2"],
        "correct": "Russians_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is Desert Fox?_2",
        "answers": ["Bagration_2", "Rommel_2", "Blucher_2", "Igorov_2"],
        "correct": "Rommel_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is best commander in history?",
        "answers": ["Napoleon", "Marmont", "Alexander", "Caesar"],
        "correct": "Caesar"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which nationality was Svetozar Borojević",
        "answers": ["Austrian", "Slovak", "Croat", "Russian"],
        "correct": "Russian"
      }
    ],
    "user": "5f67b1607df2e42008681177"
  },
  {
    "name": "Drugi seeder kviz2",
    "description": "Ovo je drugi kviz",
    "q_and_a": [
      {
        "question": "What's the price of a mile?_2",
        "answers": ["50000_2", "60000_2", "70000_2", "80000_2"],
        "correct": "50000_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who won the war of 1812?_2",
        "answers": ["Brits_2", "Americans_2", "Russians_2", "Bulgarians_2"],
        "correct": "Russians_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is Desert Fox?_2",
        "answers": ["Bagration_2", "Rommel_2", "Blucher_2", "Igorov_2"],
        "correct": "Rommel_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is best commander in history?",
        "answers": ["Napoleon", "Marmont", "Alexander", "Caesar"],
        "correct": "Napoleon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which nationality was Svetozar Borojević",
        "answers": ["Austrian", "Slovak", "Croat", "Russian"],
        "correct": "Croat"
      }
    ],
    "user": "5f67b1607df2e42008681177"
  },
  {
    "name": "Drugi seeder kviz3",
    "description": "Ovo je drugi kviz",
    "q_and_a": [
      {
        "question": "What's the price of a mile?_2",
        "answers": ["50000_2", "60000_2", "70000_2", "80000_2"],
        "correct": "50000_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who won the war of 1812?_2",
        "answers": ["Brits_2", "Americans_2", "Russians_2", "Bulgarians_2"],
        "correct": "Russians_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is Desert Fox?_2",
        "answers": ["Bagration_2", "Rommel_2", "Blucher_2", "Igorov_2"],
        "correct": "Rommel_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is best commander in history?",
        "answers": ["Napoleon", "Marmont", "Alexander", "Caesar"],
        "correct": "Alexander"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which nationality was Svetozar Borojević",
        "answers": ["Austrian", "Slovak", "Croat", "Russian"],
        "correct": "Croat"
      }
    ],
    "user": "5f67b1607df2e42008681177"
  },

  {
    "name": "Matkov prvi kviz",
    "description": "Ovo je prvi kviz",
    "q_and_a": [
      {
        "question": "What's the price of a mile?",
        "answers": ["50000", "60000", "70000", "80000"],
        "correct": "50000"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who won the war of 1812?",
        "answers": ["Brits", "Americans", "Russians", "Bulgarians"],
        "correct": "Russians"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is Desert Fox?",
        "answers": ["Bagration", "Rommel", "Blucher", "Igorov"],
        "correct": "Rommel"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is best commander in history?",
        "answers": ["Napoleon", "Marmont", "Alexander", "Caesar"],
        "correct": "Napoleon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which nationality was Svetozar Borojević",
        "answers": ["Austrian", "Slovak", "Croat", "Russian"],
        "correct": "Croat"
      }
    ],
    "user": "5f67b1c35b36690b9763ce20"
  },
  {
    "name": "Matkov drugi kviz",
    "description": "Ovo je drugi kviz",
    "q_and_a": [
      {
        "question": "What's the price of a mile?_2",
        "answers": ["50000_2", "60000_2", "70000_2", "80000_2"],
        "correct": "50000_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who won the war of 1812?_2",
        "answers": ["Brits_2", "Americans_2", "Russians_2", "Bulgarians_2"],
        "correct": "Russians_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is Desert Fox?_2",
        "answers": ["Bagration_2", "Rommel_2", "Blucher_2", "Igorov_2"],
        "correct": "Rommel_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is best commander in history?",
        "answers": ["Napoleon", "Marmont", "Alexander", "Caesar"],
        "correct": "Marmont"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which nationality was Svetozar Borojević",
        "answers": ["Austrian", "Slovak", "Croat", "Russian"],
        "correct": "Croat"
      }
    ],
    "user": "5f67b1c35b36690b9763ce20"
  },
  {
    "name": "Matkov treći kvviz",
    "description": "Ovo je drugi kviz",
    "q_and_a": [
      {
        "question": "What's the price of a mile?_2",
        "answers": ["50000_2", "60000_2", "70000_2", "80000_2"],
        "correct": "50000_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who won the war of 1812?_2",
        "answers": ["Brits_2", "Americans_2", "Russians_2", "Bulgarians_2"],
        "correct": "Russians_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is Desert Fox?_2",
        "answers": ["Bagration_2", "Rommel_2", "Blucher_2", "Igorov_2"],
        "correct": "Rommel_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is best commander in history?",
        "answers": ["Napoleon", "Marmont", "Alexander", "Caesar"],
        "correct": "Caesar"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which nationality was Svetozar Borojević",
        "answers": ["Austrian", "Slovak", "Croat", "Russian"],
        "correct": "Russian"
      }
    ],
    "user": "5f67b1c35b36690b9763ce20"
  },
  {
    "name": "Matkov najbolji kviz",
    "description": "Ovo je drugi kviz",
    "q_and_a": [
      {
        "question": "What's the price of a mile?_2",
        "answers": ["50000_2", "60000_2", "70000_2", "80000_2"],
        "correct": "50000_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who won the war of 1812?_2",
        "answers": ["Brits_2", "Americans_2", "Russians_2", "Bulgarians_2"],
        "correct": "Russians_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is Desert Fox?_2",
        "answers": ["Bagration_2", "Rommel_2", "Blucher_2", "Igorov_2"],
        "correct": "Rommel_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is best commander in history?",
        "answers": ["Napoleon", "Marmont", "Alexander", "Caesar"],
        "correct": "Napoleon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which nationality was Svetozar Borojević",
        "answers": ["Austrian", "Slovak", "Croat", "Russian"],
        "correct": "Croat"
      }
    ],
    "user": "5f67b1c35b36690b9763ce20"
  },
  {
    "name": "Matkov specijalni kviz",
    "description": "Ovo je drugi kviz",
    "q_and_a": [
      {
        "question": "What's the price of a mile?_2",
        "answers": ["50000_2", "60000_2", "70000_2", "80000_2"],
        "correct": "50000_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who won the war of 1812?_2",
        "answers": ["Brits_2", "Americans_2", "Russians_2", "Bulgarians_2"],
        "correct": "Russians_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is Desert Fox?_2",
        "answers": ["Bagration_2", "Rommel_2", "Blucher_2", "Igorov_2"],
        "correct": "Rommel_2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is best commander in history?",
        "answers": ["Napoleon", "Marmont", "Alexander", "Caesar"],
        "correct": "Alexander"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which nationality was Svetozar Borojević",
        "answers": ["Austrian", "Slovak", "Croat", "Russian"],
        "correct": "Croat"
      }
    ],
    "user": "5f67b1c35b36690b9763ce20"
  }
]
